{"data":[{"question":"You needn't to make an appointment to see the bank manager.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"needn't","b":"to make","c":"to see","d":"bank","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To make-> make","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"If you don't want Sally to be angry with you, I suggested you apologise.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"don't","c":"to be","d":"suggested","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Suggested-> suggest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"It was careful of you to leave the window open last night.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"careful","c":"to leave","d":"open","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Careful-> careless","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The train journey from London to Bristol take two hours.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"journey","b":"to","c":"take","d":"hours","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Take-> takes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"George is not nearly as energetic than he used to be.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"nearly","b":"as","c":"than","d":"be","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Than-> as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"He can speak France well enough to go to the conference.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"France","b":"well","c":"enough","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- France-> french","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"If only you had tried harder, you might pass the exam.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If only","b":"had tried","c":"might pass","d":"exam","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Might pass-> might have passed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"She was dismissed because her typing was poorly.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"dismissed","c":"typing","d":"poorly","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Poorly-> poor","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"She doesn't know the difference between margarine with butter.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"doesn't","b":"difference","c":"between","d":"with","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- With-> and","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The man in which painting bears a strong resemblance to my uncle.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"which","b":"bears","c":"strong","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Which-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}